womenworking.com 2006-11-15

# Women Working - Privacy Statement

[www.womenworking.com](http://www.womenworking.com/) is owned by Creative Expansions, Inc. We have created this Privacy Statement in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy. The following discloses the information gathering and dissemination practices for womenworking.com.

We may use your IP address to help diagnose problems with our server, and to administer our website. 

The site contains links to other sites. Womenworking.com is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of these websites. 

Our online surveys ask visitors for contact information like their e-mail address. We may use contact data from our surveys to send visitors information about our company. Users may opt-out of receiving future mailings by e-mailing us at:   
[helene@womenworking.com](mailto:helene@womenworking.com?subject=privacy-statement). 

**PUBLIC INFORMATION**

This site may make available from time to time information given to us by our visitors i.e., recommended books, strategies, comments about information appearing on the website. Please remember that this information becomes public information and you should exercise caution when deciding to disclose your personal information. 

**CONTACTING THE WEBSITE**

If you have any questions about this Privacy Statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this website, contact [helene@womenworking.com](mailto:helene@womenworking.com?subject=privacy-statement).

This Privacy Policy is subject to change. If changes occur, they will be posted here as part of this Privacy Statement.

Helene Lerner, Creative Expansions, Inc.

Helene Lerner - Team Leader  
Gail Lubin - Editor  
Nicole Ferraro - Writer  
Soma Ghoshal - Writer  
Kathleen Hennessy - Writer  
Kayla Rakowski - Writer  

Top
